He's a teacher.
And since without him, I probably
would have been executed by now.
He's also...
Technically, he's my
benefactor. Technically.
But then, he's been that for
a lot of other people, too.
Honestly, though, I don't
really know him all that well.
But one thing I know he is, for sure...
An idiot. Major idiot. Simon.
But still...
He's flippant egotistical, and it
goes without saying he's the strongest
You are my special.
Now I'm in the middle of the
world, let's go to the city!
Tokyo, the city of
Tokyo, the city of Tokyo!
I'm in the middle of the world,
let's go to the
city of Tokyo.
Love you baby!
No one mistakes to run!
walls of me
It should make you die.
Your love never.
I make it so little.
You are my special.
Oh, young man, young man.
But I'm my world's a god.
I'll never know, now, so wish you.
You won't lie there.
In the same way, to cry.
Girl, around the world.
What do you say?
You are my special.
We are special.
Hey there, weed.
This is the third time we've met, right?
And you still underestimate
the hell out of me.
I'll kill you first.
Come on now, bring it. What's wrong?
After all, you're the ones
who said not to run, right?
Did he just touch?
Need a hand.
He's only targeting Jogo.
So his earlier declaration
was just misdirection.
I also see...
He's stopped using his
limitless technique.
Has he given up on
adjusting his technique?
And started focusing on compact
attacks using cursed energy
manipulation in a space
that's filling up with humans?
Well, that just means there's no
need for me to slip into the crowd.
I can use my technique instead!
Do domain amplification! Pardon me!
Got you.
This is where you're weak.
Right.
I knew it.
You can't use domain amplification
and innate technique at the same time.
I only remain safe because I use
Domain Amplification to protect myself!
He's operating at this level with only
basic cursed energy and martial arts!
Satoru Gojo!
Is there anything you're
not capable of doing?!
He is not a cursed spirit.
I bet he's one of the incarnated
death painting wounds.
He's annoying, but he comes later.
Are you sure about this?
The more you try to neutralize my
technique with your domain amplification,
the stronger I'm forced
to maintain my technique.
I don't think this asparagus has the
How's the energy left to withstand that,
do you?
Satoru Gojo!
Look what I have here!
Hanami.
Next.
The Prison Realm is a living barrier.
It's what Genshin was reduced to.
There's nothing that cannot
be sealed in the Prison Realm.
So of course there are conditions
to sealing something in it, right?
One minute.
Huh?
Once the Prison Realm's gate is opened,
we'll have to keep Satoru Gojo within its
effective sealing range of four meters.
Make sure to keep him in there
for at least one whole minute.
I'll burn you to death!
You didn't join up with us just
to push that impossible task.
You must have some kind of alternate
agenda you're not telling us about,
but I won't let you set us up to fail.
The stakes aren't worth it.
We don't stand a chance if it means we
have to fight that thing for a full minute!
You're getting heated up, Jogo.
It's alright.
Even though we do need a minute.
Don't let Hanami's death be in vain.
Use the humans as cover and
focus on hit-and-run tactics!
Chou-chou!
If you're not going to help out,
I swear I'll kill you myself!
Yeah, yeah.
Not too close, not too far.
But that's the best they can do.
The people who can't see cursed
spirits have started avoiding me.
If their numbers keep declining and space
opens up, then I can catch Volcano Head.
No more releasing my technique
to lure it in like before.
I've revealed my goal of beating
them to a pulp in close combat.
And it'll be an issue that
keeps away and coordinates with
that death painting to unleash
a big attack through the crowd.
I'm sorry, but I can't save everyone.
So I promise.
To exorcise them instead.
It's still not time!
It has to have been
over 20 minutes by now!
Not yet.
Satoru Gojo is still completely composed.
We need to push him
much closer to the edge.
Hey there, are you okay?
Everyone turned into monsters, and
then they all got on the train.
I was told I wasn't needed
because the train was full.
So that he was in this area.
Damn.
everyone got on the
train an eight-car train
is pulling in please
wait behind the yellow
line gojo please do not
lean on the platform
doors or reach your hands past them Huh?
It's here!
Let me on the train!
Move! I'm getting in!
What are we doing?
The door's not open!
What the hell are they thinking?
Shoko!
Man, the air smells so nice.
Smells like sweet beer.
Let's leave a few humans alive after all.
We can release them into the
woods and hunt them down.
Can't I burn it down with them inside?
Hanami will get mad over that.
Well, Hanami has been killed.
Really?
I really can't hit you.
Patchbase, the one Nanami
and Yuji talked about.
Let me tell you why humans are so gross.
Well, one reason anyway.
It's that there are too many.
So there are either cursed
spirits or cursed users above us.
Idle Transfiguration, Soul
Multiplicity, Body Repel!
Satoru Gojo isn't like Yuji Itadori.
I know he's capable of cold logic.
He probably assumes
some degree of sacrifice
is necessary as he makes
certain to exercise us.
But with both the death counts and
the number of living people rising,
the skills determining what degrees
acceptable will stop functioning.
What I need you to do right now, Gojo,
is to use your infinite void to
kill us and all the people here,
so you can save the people
outside your domain.
But you're incapable of doing that.
You are only willing to
accept one type of sacrifice.
The type where people are
killed by cursed spirits,
not the type where people
are killed by Satoru Gojo.
Now, think.
Ponder it.
Focus your mind.
He's gonna do it!
Domain Expansion.
Infinite Void.
It was a desperate gamble on a domain
expansion lasting two-tenths of a second.
Two-tenths of a second was the limit
Satoru Gojo set purely on instinct.
It was the amount of time he believed
non-sorcerers could withstand
being in infinite void without becoming
vegetables or facing after-effects.
During that two-tenths of a second,
roughly half a year's worth of
information flowed into the brains
of the non-sorcerers and
transfigured humans who were present.
It rendered every one of them
unconscious while standing upright.
However, all the survivors from B-5 were
able to return to society two months later.
That's how limited his infinite void was.
Of course, that meant the special grade
cursed spirit could reawaken at any moment.
So with their potential
counterattack in mind,
Satsuru Gojo narrowed his focus
on the transfigured humans.
After dismissing his domain,
the strongest sorcerer of the
modern age slaughtered all of the
roughly 1,000 transfigured humans
unleashed upon B5 in 299 seconds.
I don't know.
Prison Realm, gate open.
It's all right, even
though we do need a minute.
Hey, Satoru.
Long time no see.
A fake...
A transformation technique.
No, it's really him.
It's only a minute in Satoru Gojo's mind.
You shouldn't lose yourself in thought.
Not in the midst of battle, Satoru!
I can't sense any cursed energy.
I can't get my body to move either.
Is this checkmate?
So, who the hell are you?
I'm Suguru Code.
Don't you remember me?
How sad.
Your body and cursed energy.
All the information provided by my six
eyes is telling me you're Suguru Code.
But...
Let both my heart and
my soul know otherwise!
Now answer me already!
Who the hell are you?!
Creepy.
How could you possibly tell?
That's my technique, you see.
I can pass from one body to another
by replacing its brain with myself.
Of course, I can also use the
techniques of the body I inhabit.
I really wanted this man's curse
manipulation in this situation.
Tell the truth.
You didn't have Shoko Ieri dispose of
Suguru Gato's body that day, did you?
An odd time for you to show consideration.
Thanks to that, I was able to
obtain this body with ease.
You needn't worry.
I'll release your seal eventually.
Really?
A hundred.
No, maybe a thousand years.
You're just too strong to be let loose.
And you're in the way of my current plans.
Have you forgotten something?
Who do you think beat
the crap out of that body
before I eventually
stepped in and killed it?
Yuta Kotsu, huh?
I just don't see as much
appeal in that boy as you do.
Copying techniques without any conditions
and a bottomless well of cursed energy.
Both of those were just
effects obtained from
binding the soul of his
most beloved with a pact.
I'm sorry to say this, but Yuta
Okotsu could never replace you.
Good night, Satoru Gojo.
So, let us meet again in the new world.
What's the matter?
There's something in my ear.
Can you hear me, Yuji Itadori?
There's no time.
I'm only going to say this once.
Satoru Gojo has been sealed.
It's time for me to choose the right way.
I'm trying to make sure
it's hard to say it's hard.
I don't want to say it's
hard to say
it's hard.
Thank you.
What do you think of skin care?
What?
You're asking me that?
Not that I mind.
I do all kinds of things, but like,
it ultimately comes down to genetics.
I'm sure those with pale,
smooth skin like Gojo would
say I don't really do anything.
Next time, pandemonium.
What do you do?
Nothing, really.